756 West Peachtree Street, CODA E1011 Atlanta, GA 30332 U.S.A.

ChangSeok Oh

Profile: https://shivamidow.github.io E-mail: changseok@gnome.org Mobile: +1 (404) 740-7896

Open-source enthusiast and hacker specializing in web technology and Linux-based systems. A WebKit and GNOME project contributor. 8 years of industry and 6 years of academic experience. Looking for opportunities in the Web browser, Emerging Web Technologies, Browser Security, Web Security & Privacy, Kernel, and Computer Graphics.

Skills

WebKit, Blink/Chromium, GNOME, Linux, C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Objective-C, Java, OpenGL/OpenGL ES, Clutter, Computer Graphics, GTK+, eBPF, BCC, Ethereum, Git, OBS, Clang, LLVM, GStreamer, Tizen, Linux Perf, Bluetooth LE, ReactJS, React Native, Embedded system, Puppeteer

Education

08/2017 - 12/2022 Ph.D. student (ABD) in Computer Science, Georgia Institute of Technology, U.S.A. 08/2017 - 12/2022 Dual M.S. in Computer Science and Cybersecurity, Georgia Institute of Technology, U.S.A. Dual B.E. in Digital Media and Computer Engineering, Ajou University, South Korea 03/2000 - 06/2008

Professional Experience

06/2019 - present	Intern at Igalia, S.L. in A Coruña, Spain
	Bring ANGLE backend for WebGL to WebKitGTK
	Zero copy texture sharing between Mesa and ANGLE via Linux DMA buffer
	Research Text-To-Speach technologies to employ for WebKitGTK
05/2020 - 08/2020	Intern at Samsung Research America in Mountain View, CA
05/2019 - 08/2019	Build a web app for health data analysis with ReactJS (frontend) and Node.js (backend)
	• Built an automated system verifying the UI of a watch app by using the Tizen automation framework
	Profiled memory usage and revealed possible memory leak of a watch app by using Valgrind
	Implemented file transfer via Bluetooth LE in a React Native watch application
08/2012 - 03/2016	Software engineer at Collabora Ltd. in Cambridge, UK
	Developed hardware-based compositing based on Clutter in WebKit
	• Resource-efficient web browser based on GNOME Epiphany for Raspberry Pi 2+
	• Customized WebKit features and API set for Smart TV Alliance SDK
07/2008 - 08/2012	Assistant Software engineer at Samsung Electronics in Suwon, South Korea
	• Developed an in-house web layout engine for Smart TVs, Printers in C++
	• Implemented WebGL and Accelerated Compositing in WebKit EFL by using OpenGL ES for Tizen
07/2007 - 06/2008	Intern at Samsung Software Membership in Suwon, South Korea
	Developed a 3D racing game using DirectX on Windows (video)

Academic Experience			
05/2021 - 08/2021	Research Intern at Tandon School of Engineering, New York University		
	Research an online ad privacy issue with Prof. Damon McCoy		
08/2019 - 05/2021	Teaching Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech		
, , ,	• CS 6262: Network Security, Design and Implement the XSS task using node.js and Chrome Extension		
	• CS 6035: Intro to InfoSec		
08/2017 - present	Research Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech		
	Study privacy leakage in online ads		
	 Redesign chromium to block user tracking by web browser fingerprints 		
	• Debloat chrome browser with feature sunsetting on the fly by binary rewriting		
	• Developed a defense system against micro DDoS by profiling resources with HPC (Intel PCM, MBM)		
	• Implemented an idle profiler that diagnoses off-CPU time in the multi-threaded programs using HPC		

O

Open Source Projects		
04/2013 - present	Committer at WebKit (patches)	
	• Implement several web features for WebKitGTK (e.g., Form validation, Gamepad API with libmanette,	
	AVIF support with dav1d, Web Speech with Flite, etc)	
	Implement OpenGL ES backend for Accelerated Compositing.	
	• Developed memory pressure handler that copes with out-of-memory on top of Linux cgroup.	
	Enhance WebGL support and Fix layout and rendering issues	
	• Fix CVE security bugs in WebKit (CVE-2020-10018, CVE-2020-11793)	
10/2013 - present	Member at GNOME Foundation (patches)	
_	Translate GNOME Web and its Help document in Korean	
01/2015 - present	Contributor at Chromium/Blink (patches)	
	Implemented a CSS spec called font-size-adjust	
	Fix layout and rendering issues in Blink	

Publications

ACSAC 2022 ACM CCS 2022 ACM CCS 2020 arXiv:2205.00056	DeView: Confining Progressive Web Applications by Debloating Web APIs (To Appear) Cart-ology: Intercepting Targeted Advertising via Ad Network Identity Entanglement (paper) Slimium: Debloating the Chromium Browser with Feature Subsetting (paper) Mitigating Low-volume DoS Attacks with Data-driven Resource Accounting (paper)	
Patents		
US 20110296323 US 20110289110 US 20110093606 US 20110090165	Web page management method and apparatus and storage medium thereof Method of re-searching webpage and apparatus and storage medium therefor Interface method and display device Interface method and display device	
Talks		
11/09/2022 12/07/2014 09/29/2014 04/25/2014 10/27/2013	Jeju University in Jeju, South Korea (slides)	
Service		
10/2021	Mentoring student participants in the Open-source SW Developer Competition, South Korea	

Last updated: 11/09/2022